(Sheldon:)And that ring was inscribed
with the phrase,
"This, too, shall pass."
-Hey, Cooper!
-Oh, my God.
I heard you drunk-dialed
Stephen Hawking last night?
Classic!
(Howard:)Get out of here, Barry.
(Barry:)Whatever you say...
(Emily:)...Clogzilla.
(Sheldon:)Clogzilla. That's pretty funny.
(Sheldon:)I don't think that's gonna pass.
(Answerphone:)Next message.
It's me again!
(Sheldon(voice):)I gave up string theory.
(Sheldon(voice):)You should give up black holes,
(Sheldon(voice):)and we can totally
solve crimes together!
(Answerphone:)Next message.
Do you know what's great?!
(Sheldon:)Geology.
Woo!
Look at this geode!
That's fun to say!
Gee... ode! Gee... ode!
(Answerphone:)Next message.
Gee... ode!
(Sheldon(voice):)I kiss girls now.
(Answerphone:)Next message.
Hey, guess who I am!
Beep, bop, boop, bop!
I'm you! Get it?!
(Answerphone:)Next message.
(Sheldon(voice):)Are you mad at me?
(Sheldon(voice):)Oh, no, you're mad at me.
I'm so sorry!
Beep, bop, boop, bop!
(Answerphone:)Next message.
(Sheldon(voice):)Thiospinel sulfide.
Thiospinel sulfide.
(Sheldon(voice):)That's even more fun
than gee... ode.
(Sheldon(voice):)Hey, did you see
The LEGO Movie?
(Stephen Hawking:)What a jackass.